You see one of multiple generated videos
The montage of this video is rebuilt every time you refresh the page
Videos emerge from the nooks of archives over the years
WORK HARD
PLAY HARD
THE MANTRA OF LATE CAPITALISM
THE MANTRA OF POST-SOVIET AUTHORITARISM
POP SONG LINE
EXCESS PLEASURE
EXHAUSTION
"Work Hard! Play Hard!" is a self-organized platform,
that includes an annual event in Minsk,
online glossary,
collective writing,
archive
and something else
Sometimes is also embodied
in posters,
slogans
speculative schemes
and performative seminars.
It came from desire
It became possible
thanks to the support and mutual aid of our friends and colleagues
It came from a desire to work and be together
in Belarus,
inviting comrades
from other countries,
weave different groups
and occupy unusual spaces
The code collects random pieces of eventfulness from the past
work hard play hard is a scheme,
diagram of tensions stretched between people and contexts,
between affective labor
and yesterday's unalienated celebration,
production drama
and dispersed collectivity.
Tensions as frictions
and tensions as the potentiality of a compressed spring.
can you imagine the moment of its release?
this video is a question
the question to the one who is watching it now
WORK HARD
PLAY HARD
THIS MESSAGE TO ALL
NOT-WORKING
ALIENATED FROM LABOR
SOCIAL PARASITES
PRECARIOUS
STRIKING
RESISTANT
SURVIVING
PROCRASTINATING
THIS IS A MESSAGE TO EVERYONE WHO QUESTIONS EXACTING LABOUR AND EXHAUSTIVE LEISURE
OUR RHYTHMS, OUR TIMES, OUR CALENDARS
DIFFERENT FROM THE IMPOSED
OUR CELEBRATIONS, OUR EVENTS
TIK TOK TIK TOK TIK TOK
OUR SALUTS AT 11:34 PM
BOOM BAM BOOM BAM
NIGHTS AND DAYS
ALL TO ALL
WORK LESS
PLAY LESS
WHPH works with issues of work and leisure,
collective practices
and co-living,
non-institutional infrastructures,
technologies
and knowledge
through performative, participatory and discursive
Formats.
It is impossible to talk about WHPH alone
impossible to tell in one language.